

GARIMA MISHRA

BUSINESS
DEVELOPMENT
EXECUTIVE

Contact

Address INDIA

Phone +91-9170871205

E-mail MGARIMA713@GMAIL.COM

Skills

PROBLEM SOLVING,
PRESSURE HANDLING,
TEAMWORK, EMPATHY,
CUSTOMER SERVICE,
COMPUTER
SKILLS, LANGUAGE SKILL

I am a Business Development Executive with 3 years of experience in Financial company Globe Money, and one year of experience in Health care company Cryoviva. I have a total 4 years of experience, I have also done short term projects and training in Marketing and Hr.

I have also attended National and International conferences, and have got First Prize in International conference held in Indra Gandhi Prathisthan Lucknow.

Work History

2017-01 -2020-07

BUISNESS DEVELOPMENT EXECUTIVE

GLOBE MONEY, LUCKNOW

Leads were provided by the company, and we called on those leads, and tried to open Demat accounts of customers. The company has also tie-up with different companies like MAX BUPA, SUN PHARMA LIFE INSURANCE etc.I tried to sell the Life and Health insurance of these companies, and generated revenue from that.

2016-03 -2016-11

BUISNESS DEVELOPMENT EXECUTIVE

CRYOVIVA, GURUGRAM
CRYOVIVA is a STEM CELL PRESERVATION
COMPANY, where we got the leads on CRM portal,
and we called on those leads, and tried to
convince the parents to preserve their child stem
cells in our company, and we generated revenue
from that.

Education

2011-08 -

2015-07

2007-06 - 2008-06	High School Diploma GIRLS GOVERNMENT INTER COLLEGE - LAKHIMPUR KHERI U.P.
2008-07 - 2009-07	SENIOR SECONDARY EDUCATION: PCB GIRLS GOVERNMENT INTER COLLEGE - LAKHIMPUR KHERI U.P.

BTECH: Biotechnology

AMITY UNIVERSITY LUCKNOW - LUCKNOW

2020-08 -2022-07

MBA: MARKETING AND HR

PRANVEER SINGH INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY -KANPUR

Certifications

2020-06	Digital marketing certificate
2021-06	Certificate course in human resource
2013-10	National conference
2014-02	International conference
2021-06	Fundamental of hr

singing, travelling, poem writing

I like to sing Bollywood songs, Love to write Hindi poems like- MAA, BETIYAN.., I have travelled many places like- ORISA, RAMESHWARAM, DWARIKA, KEDARNATH, BADRINATH ..and many other places..

Additional Information

I have computer proficiency also- CCC MS OFFICE BASIC EXCEL